<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Whiskers and Ferments</title>
    <link>http://whiskersandferments.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Whiskers and Ferments</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:30:29 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://whiskersandferments.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://whiskersandferments.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:30:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://whiskersandferments.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact me via email at: fabianbusse635(at)gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://whiskersandferments.com/posts/init-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:30:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://whiskersandferments.com/posts/init-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello! You catched me in my natural habitat!
Welcome to this small blog.
if you are new here then I probably sent you the link I guess. Anyways.. welcome here and great that you visit :)
This website is meant to be mostly for me to have an easy and quick option to save and share my ideas, recipes and experiments with the world. So don&amp;rsquo;t be confused. It can get weirdly and confusing here, since I don&amp;rsquo;t really have an idea of what I am doing here either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s me</title>
      <link>http://whiskersandferments.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:30:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://whiskersandferments.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, fellow food explorers and digital wanderers! It&amp;rsquo;s me! By day, I&amp;rsquo;m the tech guy, and by night, I&amp;rsquo;m trying my best to work with the magic of culinary experiences in my kitchen!
You might be wondering, how does someone go from debugging code to fermenting cabbages? Well, it&amp;rsquo;s simple: I believe in the power of synergy! Just like how a good tech stack needs the right components, my recipes rely on the perfect blend of locally sourced ingredients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://whiskersandferments.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 23:30:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://whiskersandferments.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.
We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy has been created with the help of the Free Privacy Policy Generator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
